my name is Zach.
I work full time at a marketing agency.
At Bad Marketing,
as a direct response copywriter.
I mostly do email copy,
but I do a little of in between
And then I have a couple of freelance
clients on the side as well. Awesome.
And what's been your
experience in Genesis so far?
My experience has been awesome.
Like, I've been in Genesis,
I think since, like, the first month
you guys launched.
In between all the trainings
and the feedbacks,
like, it's been incredible.
And with all the new AI stuff, it's
been awesome because balancing
the agency work with freelance clients
and having all these bots makes
everything faster for me
so I can get more work done in less time.
But it's still top quality work.
I just landed a new client,
a couple months ago,
after going through, like,
a whole death match week by week
kind of scenario,
using the bots to
to help me get a bunch of work
done in less time.
And I think
the coolest thing for me is like,
no matter what
project I want to try and tackle,
there's a plethora
of trainings
or videos or bots at my disposal.
So even though I usually do email stuff,
if I want to get into VSL’s
or ads or advertorials or anything
in between like I've got,
you know, nearly
unlimited resources at my disposal.
Amazing.
And what has been
the most valuable part of Genesis?
I think when I first started,
the most valuable part
was the feedback on my copy.
Like I'd be able to submit copy and stuff
like that.
Kind of ongoing.
It's just been like some of the core
trainings you guys have done.
And like,
there's still some that I go back to
and reference different frameworks
or examples, like all the time.
And then most recently, for me,
just with my workload
expanding, it's been all the AI bots.
nice
Do you have a favorite bot
or workflow of bots
that you use?
I mostly use the click driver bot.
Because like one of my clients
that I write for, it's very short,
punchy, like Clickbank style offers
and it works awesome.
Lately, I've used like the Mario
and the Luke bot a lot just to like
as my own little marketing strategist
So like I'm trying to figure out how
I want to organize something.
It's a really great resource
to go back and forth
with someone like instantaneously.
So Amazing.
I don't know any, any results or anything
tangible that you able to do,
with Genesis, with the bots?
Yeah.
I mean, well, so through the agency job
alone,
like between all my clients, I’ve generated
like seven figures in revenue,
which was like a big thing for me
because, like, now I call myself a seven
figure, you know, copywriter.
And all of that is basically
a byproduct of, like,
where I am now as a copywriter compared to
I think it was almost three years ago
that I joined,
it's like night and day difference.
And then being able to work with some of
the bigger named people in the industry
based on the merit of my copy is
is pretty cool. Awesome.
You were also able to win
a copywriting challenge as well.
Correct? Yeah.
Nice and what.
Yeah. What was that challenge?
So basically it was like
four weeks, and then every week
we had to write
like a set number of emails.
And those emails
kind of increased in terms of the amount.
and they were
also for different offers.
So I was able to use
like the copyblock stuff,
that you guys talk about
and the click driver’s emails
just to quickly get it done.
Because we had to get it done
from like Tuesday to Friday,
I think was the timeframe.
And week over week.
Yeah. I just kept passing on
and then I won.
And since then, I've written
some pretty good bangers for them.
So that's awesome.
Yeah, that's such
a huge accomplishment.
So I think you had a win
every week, right?
You know, I had to like. Yeah.
It was like top emails move on.
So, like,
I was chosen out of, like, 80 people
like to be in the final eight
or whatever to do this thing.
And then I was the
the winner by the end of it.
That's awesome. Yeah, that's key.
And that's the thing that I see with AI
and with the bots in general, is
It just amplifies
whatever talent that you have
and allows you to do more at scale
and with more volume.
And go deeper with stuff.
That's been my experience at least.
So that's an awesome accomplishment.
Cool.
your experience just overall
with the community, with the culture,
with the trainings inside of Genesis
as compared with,
other trainings or other programs
the community is great.
I mean, and to be fair, like,
I probably don't even interact in it
as much as I could
and I would definitely
get more benefit from it.
the community is great,
like between you and Mario
and then just everybody else in it
it's like a very supportive.
You know sometimes
like some of these other communities
I've been in like
it feels a little cutthroat or like other
people are trying to always pitch you
something or, I don’t know
it doesn't seem as genuine.
But that hasn't been my experience
with Genesis.
it's been pretty great.
And again, like, it's
another resource where
I can go pose a question to the group.
And before you or Mario
even have a chance to get to it,
like I'll have several other people,
you know, jumping in and
and dropping their thoughts
and help and stuff.
Awesome.
I mean, and anything else
that you want to share
about your experience
or you think would be helpful
for somebody
who's considering joining Genesis?
I would do it.
I mean, whether you're a freelancer,
just kind of an all-around marketer,
or even if it's just your launching
your own business.
Again, I've been a member
for almost three years.
I've never once considered canceling
My ROI has been infinite.
I mean, just landing the one gig for me
kind of pays off
almost the entire three years
in and of itself.
So, I think it's totally worth it.
Just the amount of guys,
the amount of stuff
you guys put in there.
I can't imagine anybody interested in
marketing would join it
and not be overwhelmed with,
you know, opportunities.